http://www.ottawalittletheatre.com/privacy/

Call today for tickets!
613-233-8948|foh@ottawalittletheatre.com
FacebookTwitterYoutube
TICKETSSUBSCRIBEDONATE
About UsGovernanceOur MissionCommittees and RepresentativesBoard of DirectorsBoard ManualMembersPrivacy PolicyAccessibility PolicyAnnual ReportsPast ProductionsCornerstone InducteesHistoryLooking BackMartha The Ghost100th Season ExhibitsOLT’s History BookBox OfficeSubscriptionsGroup RatesSeating MapParkingFAQMiss Daisy Club2019-2020 SeasonAuditionsUpcoming AuditionsRehearsal ScheduleAudition TipsLearning@OLTTheatre TrainingEODL FestivalOLT TechsVolunteerGet involvedVolunteer RolesRespectful Workplace PolicyProduction ResourcesSupport OLTSponsorshipPreviewsFundraisingSeason DonationsContact UsNewsOLT NewsEODL News
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Julie-Anne
2019-09-26T15:39:23+00:00
Privacy of Information
Purpose
OLT is committed to respecting the personal information of its patrons, members, donors, volunteers, staff, Board members, web-users and other stakeholders:
per the requirements of federal and provincial laws, specifically, the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA)
these laws are to be regularly reviewed and the policy updated.
All staff and agents are bound by agreement to comply with this policy, both during and after their employment, and are encouraged to identify situations or procedures that may cause personal information to be at risk.
The Board may vary the application of this policy to limit or refuse the disclosure of the information.
Personal Information
OLT collects personal information from ticket-buyers, members, donors, volunteers and others by electronic media (e-mail, web access, etc), telephone, paper-based, and in person. This information is stored in our ticketing, volunteer and other databases and in hard copy files.
Personal information is: any information that can be used to distinguish, identify or contact a specific individual – including an individual’s opinions or beliefs, and
is used only to better serve patrons and to expand volunteering:
providing information, re: tickets, memberships, donations ongoing events and news
thanking supporters, issue tax receipts
inviting supporters to special events
soliciting subscriptions and donations.
Personal information is not:
publicly available information – addresses and telephone numbers as published in telephone directories
organizational information – the name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization
information that does not identify individual persons, such as web traffic, surveys and demographics.
Unless still in use, or required by law to be preserved, financial and sensitive information must be destroyed no more than two years after it is collected.
Only authorized personnel have access to personal information.  Every effort will be made to protect information from unauthorized physical and electronic access:
individual financial details re level of financial support may only be published with their consent
financial or credit card information can only be confirmed, not released
system access passwords must be maintained to industry standards
physical data (paper, computers, etc.) must be secured – stored in the safe or locked cabinets – from theft or unauthorized disclosure
remote back-up or external system must be to industry-standard encryption and limited to functions critical to theatre operations.
Unneeded personal information must be made anonymous or destroyed:
physical data should be shredded/destroyed
archives of financial/ticketing information in a secure format/location
electronic media must be destroyed/ wiped, including any drives, memory device or systems.
On request, individuals may have access to and be informed about the use of their information
OLT never sells or rents personal information to any third party. Information can only be provided to another organization on written agreement, to ensure:
protection of information and assume responsibility for any injury if this policy is not followed
a record is kept of shared information for a period of 3 years
data collected about patrons on behalf of third parties should be treated in a similar manner to OLT patron data
this responsibility is to supersede internal policies and usage of information.
Adopted April 21, 2004.  Revised/approved January 31st, 2009 and November 27, 2017
Subscribe to the Ottawa Little Theatre e-newsletter
Leave this field empty if you're human:
